export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "Which language runs in a web browser?",
        options:[ "Java", "C", "Python", "JavaScript"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following command is used to create react-js-app ?",
        options:["npx create-react-app appname", "npm install create-react-app", "npx install create-react-app -g ", "install - l create-react-app"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
        options: ["Create", "Extends", "Inherits", "Delete"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default port number in which the application run ?",
        options: ["3000", "8080", "3050", "3030"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
        options: ["State & Props", "Services & Components", "State & Services", "State & Component"],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is must for the API in React.js ?",
        options: ["SetinitialComponent", "renderComponent", "render", "All of the above"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",
        options: ["Compiler", "Transpilar", "Both of the above", "None of the above"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question:  "In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
        options:["SetState", "Render with arguments", "Props", "PropTypes"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following function is true about changing the state in React.js ?",
        options:["this.State{}", "this.setState", "this.setChangeState", "All of the above"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?",
        options:["self()", "inherits()", "this()", "super()"],
        answer: 4
    },
];